tigernet.com 2019-05-19

# Disclaimer | TigerNet

### DISCLAIMER

TigerNet.com is dedicated to providing information about Clemson Tigers. It is in NO WAY endorsed by Clemson Tigers. The opinions and information expressed throughout this page are purely those of the authors and intended for entertainment purposes only. While this page provide links to other sites, the information located at those sites is neither maintained by nor endorsed by the authors of this page. 

### PRIVACY STATEMENT

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/tigernet.com).  
TigerNet believes that electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. We recognize the confidentiality of information that may be disclosed by members in registering and we are firmly committed to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this site. 

**Does TigerNet ask for personal information?**  
Yes. TigerNet asks for your name, e-mail address, and other limited personal information when you sign up as a member and use features such as chat and the message board. We may ask for similar information at other times, such as when you enter sweepstakes or other promotions sponsored by TigerNet and/or our many partners. 

**How Does TigerNet use my personal information?**  
TigerNet will use registration information to let you know about new features or other offers of interest from TigerNet, or to address customer service needs and requests. In distributing advertiser or sponsor messages, the advertiser never has access to individual account information. TigerNet does not sell, rent or otherwise distribute the personal information you provide us to these advertisers. Advertisers simply provide an insertion order for the advertising message and TigerNet then displays the ad to appropriate users based on the criteria specified in the order. 

**Will TigerNet disclose any of my personal information to third parties?**  
TigerNet will not disclose any of your personal information, except with your knowledge and consent as described in this policy or as may be required by law, or to protect the rights or property of TigerNet. TigerNet reserves the right to disclose aggregated user statistics, such as "45% of our users are female" or "47% of our users earn $50,000 or more per year" in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties. Additionally, if you click away from TigerNet to visit the site of any third party advertiser or sponsor, you may be asked for your credit card or other personal information in order to purchase or use products and services offered. These companies have their own privacy and data collection practices. TigerNet has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies. You should therefore review their privacy policies carefully if you have concerns about how your information may be used. 

**Does TigerNet use "IP Addresses" and cookies?**  
IP Addresses: We do use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site, and also to help distinquish between certain userids ion the interactive areas. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information such as geographic distribution of our members. 

**TigerNet Cookies:**  
Contrary to popular myth, cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computers memory, but rather, record only information you volunteer to us upon registering or visiting the site. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you register at our Web site that enable our server to recognize or "remember" who you are each time you return. TigerNet may make limited use of cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. For instance we often save your password so it doesnt have to be re-entered each time you login. 

**Advertiser Cookies:**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

This site, TigerNet, uses the services of Adtegrity.com for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Adtegrity collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Adtegrity, including your ability to opt out of the system, go to <http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp>. 

To learn more about behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

While we do use cookies in other parts of our Web site as explained above, cookies received with banner ads may or may not be collected by our company or be under our control. 

TigerNet.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. 

**Member Profiles**  
Demographic data is collected at our site at the users option. This information may include age and gender and other personal preferences that can be viewed and tabulated for use in marketing TigerNet to advertisers and others. In no case is personal information given or sold to third parties. TigerNet controls the distribution of ALL information at the site. 

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact: 

Tommy Crumpton  
PO Box 1053   
Central, SC 29630 

Submit Feedback
